[THEME MUSIC PLAYING]
[SCREAMING IN PAIN]
[TIRES SCREECHING]
- [ENGINE REVVING]
- [TIRES SCREECHING]
[TIRES SCREECH]
[ENGINES REVVING]
[TRUCK HORN BLARES]
[LOUD CRASH]
[TIRES SCREECHING]
- Stop!
- [GUNSHOTS]
[FIREWORKS EXPLODING]
[METAL RODS CLANGING]
- [ENGINE REVVING]
- [BUS HORN HONKS]
[GLASS SHATTERING]
- [TIRES SCREECHING]
- [LOUD CRASH]
[ENGINES REVVING]
[TIRES SCREECHING]
[GUNSHOTS]
- [TRUCK HORN HONKS]
- [LOUD CRASH]
[TIRES SCREECHING]
Sam needs a father
who will guide her.
She needs you desperately.
You violated
your agency's protocol?
We caught Mr. Chan.
We're so close
to solving this case.
You know how much the name
you bear means to me.
I will give you one more chance.
The moment you tarnish
my name,
I'll disown you as my daughter.
You've waited so long for this.
He took advantage
and belittled me.
The day will come where
the tables will turn.
Gabo, tell me the truth.
I took on a sideline.
I got some gold, Pa.
When I got it,
I got second thoughts about
whether I should return it.
I felt guilty.
I chose to do the right thing.
I'm so proud of you, Gabo.
You've made me so happy.
I feel sorry for you, Gabo.
You shouldn't have to experience
a life like this.
[SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING]
Do you still remember...
when you were a child,
our life was luxurious?
But...
It all disappeared.
[SOMBER MUSIC CONTINUES]
I remember, Pa.
I remembered everything.
[SIGHS]
A Japanese man
once asked
for my help to look
for a treasure.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
Nice!
Sir! Good evening!
- Sorry to keep you waiting.
- It's alright, sir.
Don't worry. Be happy.
That's why you're my favorite.
- Let's go, sir.
- Let's go.
[ENGINE HUMMS]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
[TIRES SCREECH]
Get in!
[GRUNTS]
- Give me your wallet!
- What are you doing?
- [SCREAMING]
- [BONES CRUNCHING]
- [BLOW LANDS]
- [GRUNTS]
- [GROANS]
[GROANS]
- [GRUNTS]
- [BLOW LANDS]
[POLICE SIREN BLARING]
- [GRUNTS]
- [KNIFE SWISHES]
[GROANS]
[POLICE SIREN BLARING]
- [GRUNTS]
- [BLOW LANDS]
- Stop!
- [GUNSHOTS]
- [GROANS]
- Put your hands up!
- Sir...
- Get down!
[YOUNG RICARDO] Put
your hands up!
Sir Tanaka!
Treasure...
G-Gold...
Sir!
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
What are you doing here, Rudy?
Thank goodness
we were doing our rounds.
You could've gotten hurt.
[YOUNG RICARDO] What's that?
Sir.
A treasure map.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
I've been working for Tanaka
for a few months, sir.
That's why I know about the
treasure they're looking for.
We heard that there are
a lot of Japanese people here.
But how do we know that
that map is real?
Tanaka's father was a soldier.
He had a lot of meetings.
From what I've heard,
there's a ton
of gold and jewelry.
He's looking for statues
made of gold, sir.
The newspaper said that there
were businessmen, politicians,
and treasure hunters silently
digging up in provinces.
And they all come back rich!
In fact, there's a group
that's looking for it in here.
But now that Tanaka is gone...
no one will fund
the search anymore.
If it were me,
I'd invest in this.
This is an absolute jackpot!
But the problem is...
I don't have
the budget for it.
What do you need
for you to find this treasure?
[YOUNG MARIANO] Oh no, sir...
you'll need
a lot of money for that.
You'll pay for the people,
food--
[YOUNG RUDY] Sir,
if we get lucky,
we could get a million
in return.
It could come back double, sir.
This chance comes
once in a lifetime.
This comes once in a lifetime.
Fine. I'll finance it.
But when we find
this treasure,
we'll have to split it.
Sixty.
Forty.
I can trust you,
right, Rudy?
As if I wasn't
your former asset, sir.
Sir, cheers.
- Cheers.
[HOST] And now, the moment
everyone is waiting for,
the Golden Star of the night,
Belinda!
[ROMANTIC MUSIC PLAYING]
[RUDY] When I first saw
your mother,
I was enchanted by her beauty.
And I told myself that
I would marry this woman.
[ROMANTIC MUSIC CONTINUES]
[CHEERING, APPLAUDING]
[CLUB MUSIC PLAYING]
- Sir, I'll just use the toilet.
- Okay.
Thank you.
[CLUB MUSIC CONTINUES]
Hi, boss!
You're so pretty, my love!
[BELINDA] Just tonight?
Not just tonight.
You're always pretty.
I knew you were coming,
so I dolled up.
[YOUNG RUDY] I promised
that when I get the gold,
I'd come back for Belinda
and help her
get out of this rut.
I vowed to give her
a better life
and devote all my love
to her.
Rudy, how many weeks
do you think it will take?
[YOUNG RUDY]
Looking at the map, sir,
there are a lot of tunnels
and passages.
- [PICKAXES, SHOVELS THUNKING]
- [MINERS GRUNTING]
[YOUNG RUDY]
Watch your head, sir. Careful.
[YOUNG MARIANO]
Hey! Don't slack off!
[YOUNG RUDY]
Give me...
Give me six to ten months, sir.
Careful, sir.
[PICKAXES, SHOVELS THUNKING]
- Sir.
- Rudy.
[YOUNG MARIANO]
Sir, give them a deadline.
They might just be stalling
so you'd keep them employed.
That's not true, sir.
[YOUNG RUDY]
I also want to find the gold.
I can't wait to find it
to finally turn my life around.
[YOUNG RICARDO]
Me, too. I can't wait.
Because I've got so many plans
for that treasure.
[YOUNG RICARDO SIGHS]
[PICKAXES, SHOVELS THUNKING]
[YOUNG RUDY]
We dug for several weeks.
We kept looking for gold.
- Dude!
- This is hopeless! I quit!
[MINER GRUNTS]
My fellow miners
slowly lost hope.
But I didn't stop.
Because I believed
that I will find the gold
that will change my life.
I don't think
we'll find it here.
- But the map says it's here.
- There's nothing here.
- Rudy!
- Bring him to the base!
[YOUNG MARIANO] Rudy!
[YOUNG RICARDO] Well?!
- Sir.
- We've been digging for weeks
and still nothing!
We're slowly losing our men!
Sir, the map says
it's here somewhere.
Do you really know
how to read a map?
Perhaps that map's fake
and you're just deceiving us.
Sir, I am not deceiving you.
I can feel it. We're so close
to finding that treasure!
But it looks like we're just
wasting our time and money here.
Let's just go home.
It's not worth the effort!
Are we really going
to give up now, sir?
Now, when we're so close
to finding the treasure?
That's the problem with you.
You keep saying
we're so close to finding gold,
but where is it?!
I'm bleeding money, Rudy!
Sir, just give me one more day.
Please, sir.
We've almost scoured
the whole cave, sir.
You've lost your mind!
Let's go home!
- Come on.
- Sir!
Sir, if you stop looking now,
you're going to regret it.
I'm already
regretting this, Rudy.
I shouldn't have believed you!
I thought you were bold.
It turns out you're
too afraid to gamble.
You're giving up
too easily.
You think I'm giving up?
You're a coward!
- [BLOW LANDS]
- Don't interfere!
- [BLOWS LANDING]
- [TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[BLOWS LANDING]
[SHOVEL RATTLING]
[THWACKS]
[BODY THUDDING]
[SHOVEL CLATTERS]
[GUN COCKS]
I can bury you alive here.
You don't know
who you're messing with.
[ANGSTY MUSIC PLAYING]
Come on, let's go.
Boss said it's time
to head home. Let's go!
- Let's go.
- Come on.
[SHOVEL SCRAPING DIRT]
[GLUM MUSIC PLAYING,
THEN FADES]
I'm doing this for you.
I don't know if I messed up
or if I'm just unlucky.
[RUDY]
Even I'm losing hope.
Whatever I end up finding...
[GRUNTING]
It was the only way
I could win Belinda over.
[SHOVEL SCRAPING DIRT]
[EMOTIONAL MUSIC PLAYING]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
Should I go through with it
or back out now?
[EMOTIONAL MUSIC CONTINUES]
[COIN CHIMES]
[COIN THUDDING]
Hey...
Where did you go?!
[UNEASY MUSIC PLAYING]
Hey, where are you?!
[UNEASY MUSIC CONTINUES]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
I thought you were leaving me.
[MUSIC BECOMES SUSPENSEFUL]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[HASP RATTLES]
[HAMMERING CHEST]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
[METAL CLANGING, THUDS]
[WONDROUS MUSIC PLAYING]
[RUDY]
When I saw the gold,
I got blinded by greed.
I forgot all my promises
to Ricardo.
My only thought was, "I'm going
to get rich and win your mom."
Whoo!
[WONDROUS MUSIC CONTINUES]
[DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING]
[SENSUAL MUSIC PLAYING]
[RUDY] When I got
the treasure...
I went back for Belinda.
- Sir, you're so handsome!
- You're handsome!
- Come inside, sir!
- Come in!
- [BOUNCER] Sir, good evening.
- Good evening.
[RUDY] If there was
anything greater
than the treasure I got...
It's your mom.
I did everything
to make her fall for me.
[SENSUAL MUSIC CONTINUES]
- Hey.
- [STAFF] Yes, sir?
- Bring her to my table.
- Yes, sir!
[BELINDA] Ma? You called for me?
[WOMAN] Yeah.
That man asked for you.
- He looks rich! Come! Yeah!
- Rich? Really?
Sir!
Belinda is here.
Well, I'll take my leave.
Sit down.
You're probably cold.
Huh?
- This is a first.
- What?
This.
[BELINDA CHUCKLES SOFTLY]
Usually, the men who ask for me
want me almost naked.
Well, I'm different from them.
[BELINDA CHUCKLES SOFTLY]
Mm.
It's hot.
- Mm.
- Eat slowly. You might choke.
- Drink first.
- I'm sorry.
Wait.
I've never seen you here before.
I'm from the province.
Where's your province?
I came from the province, too!
But I haven't been home
for a long time
'cause the fare's too expensive.
[SIGHS]
Instead of going there,
I just send the money
to my mom.
It's more important
that she buys her medicine
than see me.
I'm sorry.
Am I talking too much?
No, that's fine. That's fine.
Your watch is beautiful.
What's your job?
Nothing.
I'm just an heir.
An heir? Wow! Then you have
no money problems.
[BELINDA SIGHS DEEPLY]
That's why when you live
with me,
you won't worry
about money anymore.
[GENTLE MUSIC PLAYING]
I'm serious.
I can change your life.
You don't have
to work here anymore.
I'll change your world.
- What's your name?
- Rudy.
Rudy Magtibay.
[BELINDA CHUCKLING]
Your last name doesn't sound
like that of an heir's.
[BELINDA CHUCKLES]
You have to get used
to the name Magtibay.
Why?
Because it'll soon be
your last name.
Really?
Belinda...
...Magtibay.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING]
[DRAMATIC MUSIC CONTINUES]
[BELINDA EXHALES]
Why?
I can do this
for the rest of my life.
What?
Looking at you.
Just staring at you.
[BELINDA BREATHES]
- Ah.
- Hm?
- Let me.
- Hm.
[GENTLE MUSIC PLAYING]
Let's get married.
[BELINDA COUGHS]
What's with you?
Don't joke like that.
I might just start
believing you.
And then I'll start hoping.
Why won't you take me seriously?
Belinda, I want to be with you
for the rest of my life.
[BELINDA BREATHES DEEPLY]
We just got to know each other.
There are things in our lives
that only happen once.
We shouldn't let them
just slip away.
Why me?
From the moment I saw you,
I knew I wanted to spend
my life with you, Belinda.
You don't know
what I went through
just to have
this chance, Belinda.
We'll run away.
We'll forget about...
...the bad things that happened
in our past.
We'll change our lives, Belinda.
We'll have a family.
One that's happy and complete.
[GENTLE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Are you ready to be...
...Mrs. Belinda Magtibay?
[GENTLE MUSIC CONTINUES]
- Are we there yet?
- Yes, we're here.
Carding, open the gate, please!
- Who's Carding?
- Sir Rudy, good morning.
Can I look now?
- Just take one more step.
- Okay.
- There. Yes.
- Can I look now?
Wow! That's a huge house.
Whose house is it?
- It's ours.
- It's ours?!
Really?
[BRIGHT MUSIC PLAYING]
[DOOR OPENS]
[BRIGHT MUSIC CONTINUES]
- [YOUNG RUDY CHUCKLES]
- [BELINDA SQUEALS]
[BELINDA] Is this for real?
This is ours?
- [BELINDA] It's ours?
- [YOUNG RUDY] Yes.
[YOUNG RUDY]
All of this is ours!
[BELINDA] I'm so lucky
to have you.
And so does our child.
He's lucky to have you
as his father.
[BRIGHT MUSIC CONTINUES]
[YOUNG RUDY]
We're almost there.
[BELINDA GRUNTING]
[MIDWIFE] I can see the baby.
- [BRIGHT MUSIC CONTINUES]
- [BABY CRYING]
[RUDY] You, Gabriel...
are the most important blessing
your mom and I received.
Hi-yah! Hi-yah! Hi-yah!
[RUDY] You brought happiness
to our home.
That time...
there was nothing
I could want more.
You and your mom...
are my real treasure.
Rudy! Come out here!
Ricardo and I were supposed
to split this between us,
but I took his share.
- Run!
- Aah!
Love, you have to go now!
Hurry!
Mommy loves you so much.
No matter what happens,
always stay good, okay?
Don't forget everything
I taught you.
Have mercy on my family.
Take me instead.
Spare my son and husband.
- Mama!
- I need to find that cop.
He has to pay
for what he did to my mother.
- [GUNSHOTS]
- [GROANS]
Well, Samantha?!
Are you still alive?!
Have you found the guy
I got into a fight with?
He better hide
before I find him.
- [SCREAMING]
- [GUNSHOT]
If you know you're right,
you should fight for it.
Help!
Aah!
- [GRUNTING]
- [BLOWS LANDING]
Help!